let CodingQuestions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In Python, which of the following is a mutable data type?",
    answer: "List",
    options: ["Tuple", "String", "List", "Dictionary"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "What is the time complexity of inserting an element at the end of an array with n elements?",
    answer: "O(1)",
    options: ["O(1)", "O(n)", "O(logn)", "O(nlogn)"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "Which sorting algorithm has the worst-case time complexity of O(n^2)?",
    answer: "Insertion sort",
    options: ["Quick sort", "Merge sort", "Insertion sort", "Heap sort"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: " What is the default value of the boolean data type in Python?",
    answer: "False",
    options: ["True", "False", "None", "0"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the output of the following code? print(2 + 3 * 4 - 6)",
    answer: "9",
    options: ["8", "9", "14", "10"],
  },
];

let InterviewQuestions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of media queries in responsive web design?",
    answer:
      "To target specific devices and apply different styles based on their characteristics.",
    options: [
      "To specify the colors and fonts of a website.",
      "To define the layout and structure of a webpage.",
      "To handle user interactions and events on a webpage",
      "To target specific devices and apply different styles based on their characteristics.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Which HTML tag is used to link an external JavaScript file to a web page?",
    answer: "script",
    options: ["script", "link", "style", "js"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does the box-sizing property in CSS control?",
    answer: "The calculation of the box's total width and height.",
    options: [
      "The shape of the box model.",
      "The visibility of the box.",
      "The positioning of the box.",
      "The calculation of the box's total width and height.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS selector?",
    answer: "the father of my grandfather/grandmother",
    options: [
      "ID selector (#myElement)",
      "Attribute selector ([myAttribute])",
      "Tag selector(myElement)",
      "Class selector (.myElement)",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How can you optimize website performance and loading speed?",
    answer:
      "By optimizing image sizes and compressing CSS and JavaScript files.",
    options: [
      "By using a responsive design approach.",
      "By optimizing image sizes and compressing CSS and JavaScript files.",
      "By increasing the number of server requests.",
      "By using a content delivery network (CDN) for hosting the website.",
    ],
  },
];

let LogicQuestions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "If all cats are dogs and some dogs are birds, which of the following statements is definitely true?",
    answer: "Some cats are birds.",
    options: [
      "All cats are birds.",
      "All birds are cats.",
      "Some cats are birds.",
      "Some birds are cats.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "If A is taller than B, and B is taller than C, which of the following statements is true?",
    answer: "The order cannot be determined.",
    options: [
      "A is the tallest.",
      "B is the tallest.",
      "C is the tallest.",
      "The order cannot be determined.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "If all apples are oranges and some oranges are bananas, which of the following statements is definitely true?",
    answer: "Some apples are bananas.",
    options: [
      "All apples are bananas.",
      "All bananas are apples.",
      "Some apples are bananas.",
      "Some bananas are apples.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "If all triangles are squares and some squares are circles, which of the following statements is definitely true?",
    answer: "Some triangles are circles.",
    options: [
      "All triangles are circles.",
      "All circles are triangles",
      "Some triangles are circles.",
      "Some circles are triangles.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "If all birds can fly and some birds are penguins, which of the following statements is true?",
    answer: "Some penguins can fly.",
    options: [
      "All penguins can fly.",
      "Some penguins can fly.",
      "No penguins can fly.",
      "The information is insufficient to determine.",
    ],
  },
];

let SpaceQuestions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does work-life balance refer to?",
    answer: " Striking a balance between personal and professional life.",
    options: [
      " Striking a balance between personal and professional life.",
      " Working long hours to achieve career success.",
      "Prioritizing work over personal commitments.",
      "Not having any personal life outside of work.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the importance of workplace diversity and inclusion?",
    answer: "It promotes a harmonious work environment.",
    options: [
      "It increases competition among employees.",
      "It promotes a harmonious work environment.",
      " It hinders collaboration and creativity.",
      "It limits the perspectives and ideas within a company.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does a collaborative work culture promote?",
    answer: "Teamwork and shared decision-making.",
    options: [
      "Individualism and competition.",
      "Siloed departments and limited communication.",
      "Teamwork and shared decision-making.",
      "Hierarchical structures and top-down management.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does professional development entail?",
    answer: "Continuous learning and acquiring new skills.",
    options: [
      "Maintaining the status quo and avoiding growth opportunities.",
      "Rejecting feedback and not seeking improvement.",
      "Focusing solely on short-term goals and tasks.",
      "Continuous learning and acquiring new skills.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "What is the significance of open communication in the workplace?",
    answer: "It fosters transparency and trust among team members.",
    options: [
      "It is not necessary for effective teamwork.",
      "It encourages secrecy and limited information sharing.",
      "It fosters transparency and trust among team members. ",
      "It leads to misunderstandings and conflicts.",
    ],
  },
];